var examQuest = [];

examQuest[0] = {
question: "What chkdsk switch Specifies the drive letter (followed by a colon), mount point, or volume name?",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/i",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;map",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;volume",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/forceofflinefix",
answer: "C"
 };

examQuest[1] = {
question: "What SFC switch Scans integrity of all protected system files. No repair operation is performed?",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/VERIFYFILE",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/VERIFYONLY",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/VERIFY",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/V",
answer: "B"
 };
 
examQuest[2] = {
question: "What chkdsk switch Forces the volume to dismount first if necessary? All opened handles to the volume would then be invalid (implies /F)",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/i",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/x",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/f",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/dd",
answer: "B"
 };
 
 examQuest[3] = {
question: "What ipconfig switch will renew the IPv4 address for the specified adapter?",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/release",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/renew4",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/renew",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/release4",
answer: "C"
 };
 examQuest[4] = {
question: "What chkdsk switch Performs a less vigorous check of index entries? (NTFS only)",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/a",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/l",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/v",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/i",
answer: "D"
 };
 
 examQuest[5] = {
question: "What chkdsk switch Must be used with '/scan', is NTFS only, and Bypasses all online repair? all defects found are queued for offline repair (i.e. 'chkdsk /spotfix').",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/scannow",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/filename",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/forceoffline",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/forceofflinefix",
answer: "D"
 };
 
 examQuest[6] = {
question: "What ipconfig switch Modifies the IPv6 DHCP class id?",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/setclassid",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/setclassid6",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/renew6",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/IPv6",
answer: "B"
 };
 
 examQuest[7] = {
question: "What chkdsk switch Runs an online scan on the volume? (NTFS only)",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/scannow",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/scanos",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/scan",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/scanall",
answer: "C"
 };
 
 examQuest[8] = {
question: "What SFC switch Verifies the integrity of the file with full path <file>.  No repair operation is performed.",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/VERIFYFILE",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/VERIFYONLY",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/VERIFY",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/V",
answer: "A"
 };
 
 examQuest[9] = {
question: "What ipconfig command will Renew the IPv6 address for the specified adapter? ",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/renew",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/renew6",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/release",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/release6",
answer: "B"
 };
 
 examQuest[10] = {
question: "Which chkdsk command Specifies the files to check for fragmentation? (FAT/FAT32 only)",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/f",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/s",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;frag",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;filename",
answer: "D"
 };
 
 examQuest[11] = {
question: "What ipconfig command Purges the DNS Resolver cache?",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;filename",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/dnsflush",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/flushdns",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/flush",
answer: "C"
 };
 
 examQuest[12] = {
question: "ipconfig switch that Displays all the IPv6 DHCP class IDs allowed for adapter",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/showclassid6",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/showclassid",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/all",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/release",
answer: "A"
 };

 examQuest[13] = {
question: "chkdsk command that Locates bad sectors and recovers readable information (implies /F, when /scan not specified).",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/R",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/V",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/C",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/A",
answer: "A"
 };
 
 examQuest[14] = {
question: "ipconfig command that Modifies the dhcp class id.",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/setclassid6",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/setclass",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/setclassid",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/M",
answer: "C"
 };
 
 examQuest[15] = {
question: "chkdsk command that Re-evaluates bad clusters on the volume (implies /R) (NTFS only)",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/A",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/E",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/C",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/B",
answer: "D"
 };
 
 examQuest[16] = {
question: "ipconfig command to Display the contents of the DNS Resolver Cache",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/displaydns",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/release",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/all",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/contents",
answer: "A"
 };
 
 examQuest[17] = {
question: "chkdsk switch that Uses more system resources to complete a scan as fast as possible. This may have a negative performance impact on other tasks running on the system. (NTFS only, Must be used with /scan)",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/scannow",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/registerdns",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/perf",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/scanall",
answer: "C"
 };
 
 examQuest[18] = {
question: "ipconfig switch that Refreshes all DHCP leases and re-registers DNS names",
choicea: "A. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/displaydns",
choiceb: "B. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/release",
choicec: "C. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/lease",
choiced: "D. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/registerdns",
answer: "D"
 };
